Let's go back to our app now, and add a check box.
回到我们的应用 添加一个复选框
This will allow the user to select if they want the whipped cream topping on
这可以让用户选择是否想要在咖啡里
their coffee.
加生奶
It will look something like this, and then you can check this box.
它看起来会像这样 这时你可以选择这个选项
Go ahead and add a check box to the app now.
给应用添加一个复选框
This will allow the user to add a whipped cream topping
这将允许用户在他们想喝的饮料里
on their drink if they want.
添加生奶
When you click on this check box it should automatically animate to
当你选择这个复选框 它会自动变为
this state.
这个状态
Also add a header that says toppings.
给复选框加一个标题 写上 TOPPINGS（配料）
There's only one topping now, but we're going to add another one later.
这里现在只有一种配料 不过之后我们会加其他的
If you click on the order button, the order summary shows, and
如果点击 ORDER 按钮 订单详情就会显示
it's still the same as before.
它和之前的一样
Eventually, we're going to modify it so
最后 我们将要修改它
it shows whether you have the whipped cream topping or not.
来显示你是否有生奶配料
For this next coding task, just focus on adding this check box and this header.
在代码练习环节 只是把重点放在添加复选框和标题上
You haven't added a check box to the layout before,
你之前在布局上还没有添加过复选框
but here's your chance to learn.
不过这是你学习的机会
You can look up online how to do this or you can check out
你可以在网上看一下怎么做 也可以参考
the Common Android Views cheat sheet, which is linked in the instructor notes.
Common Android Views 手册 链接已经放在讲师注释里了
Whichever way you decide to figure it out,
不管你用什么方法弄明白
when your app launches it should look something like this.
当你的应用运行出来 应该是这个样子的
Also note that I would like 24dp of space in between the box and
同时请注意 我希望 CheckBox 和 Whipped cream 文字之间
the text whipped cream.
有 24dp 的留白
Also use a font size of 16sp for the whipped cream text.
Whipped cream 的字体大小是 16sp
By the way, when I draw out specific metrics like for spacing or
顺便说一下 当我制定特殊的度量值 例如空间或
font sizes or font colors, that's actually called red lines.
字体大小或字体颜色 这都会称为 Redlines
Red lines are very detailed specifications about how the visual
Redlines 是对于应用的可视化界面
appearance of the app should look like.
非常详细的说明
If you’re a developer working with a designer,
如果你是一个和设计师一起工作的开发者
you’ll probably get a set of red lines for different screens in your app so
你可能得到应用的不同屏幕尺寸的 Redlines 集
that you can build according to these specs.
这样你就可以按照这个规格构建了
The red lines may include values for colors,size of views,
Redlines 可能包含颜色 视图大小
spacing, font sizes and font colors.
间距 字体大小 字体颜色
These are the red lines for
这些 Redlines 是我们在
the sunshine app in the developing Android apps Udacity course.
Android 应用开发课程中开发 Sunshine 应用时应使用的
Keeping this in mind, go ahead and
记住这个 然后继续
start planning how you're going to build out this layout.
开始计划你将怎样构建这个布局
Remember the three steps that we taught you in lesson one for
记住我在第一课教你的关于构建布局
building any layout.
的三个步骤
First, select the views that you need.
首先 挑选你需要的视图
Then position them, and then style them.
之后放置它们 设置它们的样式
In the text boxes provided, write down what you need to do in each step.
在提供的文本框里 写下每一步你要做的东西
Once you've planned it out, then go ahead and add this to your app.
计划完成后 继续去更新你的应用吧
Ironically, I don't have a check box for
讽刺的是 这次没有表示任务完成的复选框
you to check when you're done with this task.
你不能勾选它们